carighttoknow.org 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy

California Right To Know is powered by NationBuilder, a website platform for organizing the community both online and offline. Our site allows you to join a community of people and organizations that support the right know what’s in our food and what we feed our families.

Learn more at: [www.carighttoknow.org/about](http://www.carighttoknow.org/about "Learn more about CA Right to Know")

### **About NationBuilder**

NationBuilder is the website and online service of 3dna, Corp. (“3dna,” “we,” or “us”). 3dna knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by 3dna when you use the Service, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our [Terms of Use](http://nationbuilder.com/tos "CA Right to Know Terms of Use").

### **Information We Collect**

**User-Provided Information:** You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, if you register for a NationBuilder account with the Service (including by “following,” “liking,” linking your account to the NationBuilder service, etc., on a third party website or network). If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service. You may provide us information in User Content you post to the Service. We may also retain any personal information you provide in connection with a payment made for Services. All financial information you provide in connection with a payment you make to NationBuilder may be collected and/or stored by a third party payment processor, as described in their Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy.

**Cookies Information:** When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets NationBuilder help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information about how you browse the Service to us. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Log File Information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Clear Gifs Information** : When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make NationBuilder better for our users.

**Third Party Services:** 3dna uses Google Analytics to help understand use of the Service. This service collects the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address, and their use of it is governed by their Privacy Policy.

### **How We Use Your Information**

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service.
